<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thesis on kubecloud</title><link>https://kubecloud.io/categories/thesis/</link><description>Recent content in Thesis on kubecloud</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 10:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kubecloud.io/categories/thesis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sneak preview</title><link>https://kubecloud.io/posts/2016-06-12_sneak-preview-934354cac84c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.io/posts/2016-06-12_sneak-preview-934354cac84c/</guid><description>It’s been a while since our last blog post. We have been crazy busy teaching a course about Microservices, Docker, Kubernetes, etc., using a Kubernetes Raspberry Pi cluster, named KubeCloud.
During this course we have evaluated the use of KubeCloud and how it can help students understand these different concepts. We have a lot of material that we will be sharing after the defense of our thesis at June 20th.</description></item><item><title>[Guide] Setting up a Kubernetes on ARM cluster on Raspberry Pis</title><link>https://kubecloud.io/posts/2016-04-13_-guide-setting-up-a-kubernetes-on-arm-cluster-on-raspberry-pis-baac1511be3d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.io/posts/2016-04-13_-guide-setting-up-a-kubernetes-on-arm-cluster-on-raspberry-pis-baac1511be3d/</guid><description>This blog post will walk you through the steps of setting up kubernetes-on-arm that Luxas has created. Thanks to Luxas’ project it is pretty straightforward to get Kubernetes up and running on a Raspberry Pi. This guide will walk you through a fork of Luxas’ project, that contains minor adjustments to the DNS and a couple of extra scripts.</description></item><item><title>How to build a Raspberry Pi Cluster</title><link>https://kubecloud.io/posts/2016-02-11_how-to-build-a-raspberry-pi-cluster-8af5f2f199d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 08:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.io/posts/2016-02-11_how-to-build-a-raspberry-pi-cluster-8af5f2f199d/</guid><description>This guide will provide you with the stuff you need for putting a Raspberry Pi cluster together. The first thing you need is of course some Raspberry Pis . We choose to buy the Raspberry Pi 2 Model B, which is a pretty powerful little machine compared to the older Raspberry Pi.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the blog - and shopping tech!</title><link>https://kubecloud.io/posts/2016-01-25_welcome-to-the-blog-and-shopping-tech/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 11:13:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.io/posts/2016-01-25_welcome-to-the-blog-and-shopping-tech/</guid><description>Welcome to our blog about the work we are about to begin within the subject of resilient cloud computing.
The title of our project is as follows: Resilient cloud computing in a controlled test environment
And what does that involve? That is a really good question, and a question we will start a quest for the next five month to answer this.</description></item></channel></rss>