<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kops on kubecloud</title><link>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/categories/kops/</link><description>Recent content in Kops on kubecloud</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 17:10:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kubecloud.github.io/website/categories/kops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Upgrading a HA Kubernetes Kops Cluster</title><link>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2017-11-14_upgrading-a-ha-kubernetes-kops-cluster-9fb34c441333/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 17:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2017-11-14_upgrading-a-ha-kubernetes-kops-cluster-9fb34c441333/</guid><description>The Kubernetes release cadence is fast-paced with minor releases every quarter. Awesome! But how do I keep up?
Don’t worry, Kops makes it fairly easy to update your HA production cluster without any downtime (assuming you have scaled your deployments to a minimum of 2 pods per deployment).
This blog post will walk you through upgrading your Kubernetes cluster version 1.</description></item><item><title>HA Kubernetes Cluster on AWS? — Kops makes it easy</title><link>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2017-03-12_ha-kubernetes-cluster-on-aws-kops-makes-it-easy-2337806d0311/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2017-03-12_ha-kubernetes-cluster-on-aws-kops-makes-it-easy-2337806d0311/</guid><description>In the first post of our mini-series about Kops, I demonstrated how you could set up a highly available Kubernetes cluster on AWS in an existing VPC leveraging the awesome open-source project Kops.
In order to demonstrate how this could be accomplished, I demonstrated how to set up all the networking, with VPC, subnets, route tables, etc.</description></item><item><title>Setting up a Highly Available Kubernetes Cluster with private networking on AWS using Kops</title><link>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2017-01-30_setting-up-a-highly-available-kubernetes-cluster-with-private-networking-on-aws-using-kops-65f7a94782ef/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2017-01-30_setting-up-a-highly-available-kubernetes-cluster-with-private-networking-on-aws-using-kops-65f7a94782ef/</guid><description>This is the first post in a series of Kubernetes and Kubernetes Operations (Kops) related blog posts.
The purpose of this series is to provide a guide to setting up a production ready Kubernetes environment on AWS. There exists lots of options to accomplish this; among others, Techtonic, Kismatic, StackPoint Cloud, OpenShift, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>