<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raspberry Pi on kubecloud</title><link>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/categories/raspberry-pi/</link><description>Recent content in Raspberry Pi on kubecloud</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:29:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kubecloud.github.io/website/categories/raspberry-pi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up a Kubernetes 1.11 Raspberry Pi Cluster using kubeadm</title><link>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2018-09-14_setting-up-a-kubernetes-1-11-raspberry-pi-cluster-using-kubeadm-952bbda329c8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2018-09-14_setting-up-a-kubernetes-1-11-raspberry-pi-cluster-using-kubeadm-952bbda329c8/</guid><description>It’s been a while, and I thought I would revisit my previous blog post on setting up a Raspberry Pi Kubernetes Cluster and publish an updated version of the guide with the latest version of Raspbian and Kubernetes. This is it. Some parts of this post are copy/paste from my previous post on setting up Kubernetes 1.</description></item><item><title>Setup a Kubernetes 1.9.0 Raspberry Pi cluster on Raspbian using Kubeadm</title><link>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2017-12-20_setup-a-kubernetes-1-9-0-raspberry-pi-cluster-on-raspbian-using-kubeadm-f8b3b85bc2d1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2017-12-20_setup-a-kubernetes-1-9-0-raspberry-pi-cluster-on-raspbian-using-kubeadm-f8b3b85bc2d1/</guid><description>Apparently it’s that time of the year again. Approximately a year ago I published a “state-of-the-art” how to run a Raspberry Pi Kubernetes cluster using HypriotOS and Kubernetes 1.4. Lots of things has happen during the past year, and I thought it was time to play with the Raspberry Pi cluster again.</description></item><item><title>Installing a Kubernetes 1.4 cluster on Hypriot 1.1.1 with kubeadm</title><link>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2016-12-15_installing-a-kubernetes-1-4-cluster-on-hypriot-1-1-1-with-kubeadm-b7495638610e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubecloud.github.io/website/posts/2016-12-15_installing-a-kubernetes-1-4-cluster-on-hypriot-1-1-1-with-kubeadm-b7495638610e/</guid><description>It’s been a while since our last blog post. However, we are back and again working with Kubernetes on a daily basis. This blog post will show you how to set up a Kubernetes 1.4 cluster with HypriotOS 1.1.1 and the new kubeadm tool.
Prerequisites A couple of Raspberry Pis (minimum two) A switch to connect the Raspberry Pis Cables for power and network For this tutorial we used 4 Raspberry Pi 3 and a Macbook Pro.</description></item></channel></rss>