<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on kubecloud</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on kubecloud</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:29:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up a Kubernetes 1.11 Raspberry Pi Cluster using kubeadm</title><link>/posts/2018-09-14_setting-up-a-kubernetes-1-11-raspberry-pi-cluster-using-kubeadm-952bbda329c8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 11:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2018-09-14_setting-up-a-kubernetes-1-11-raspberry-pi-cluster-using-kubeadm-952bbda329c8/</guid><description>It’s been a while, and I thought I would revisit my previous blog post on setting up a Raspberry Pi Kubernetes Cluster and publish an updated version of the guide with the latest version of Raspbian and Kubernetes. This is it. Some parts of this post are copy/paste from my previous post on setting up Kubernetes 1.</description></item><item><title>Setup a Kubernetes 1.9.0 Raspberry Pi cluster on Raspbian using Kubeadm</title><link>/posts/2017-12-20_setup-a-kubernetes-1-9-0-raspberry-pi-cluster-on-raspbian-using-kubeadm-f8b3b85bc2d1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-12-20_setup-a-kubernetes-1-9-0-raspberry-pi-cluster-on-raspbian-using-kubeadm-f8b3b85bc2d1/</guid><description>Apparently it’s that time of the year again. Approximately a year ago I published a “state-of-the-art” how to run a Raspberry Pi Kubernetes cluster using HypriotOS and Kubernetes 1.4. Lots of things has happen during the past year, and I thought it was time to play with the Raspberry Pi cluster again.</description></item><item><title>AWS re:invent 2017 — day 2</title><link>/posts/2017-11-29_aws-re-invent-2017-day-2-5d4c113a70de/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 17:05:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-11-29_aws-re-invent-2017-day-2-5d4c113a70de/</guid><description>The second day of breakout sessions. Crazy walk-up line before the first session of the day with Sam Newman on Building Microservices on AWS. Luckily I got up early and queued up 70 minutes before the talk. At this point, 20–30 people were already lined up. But I managed to get in.</description></item><item><title>AWS re:invent 2017 — Day 1</title><link>/posts/2017-11-28_aws-re-invent-2017-day-1-c4cdb5955dfc/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 03:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-11-28_aws-re-invent-2017-day-1-c4cdb5955dfc/</guid><description>The focus of my first day at Reinvent was mostly on the topic of security and financial services. Re:invent is very crowded and there’s crazy lines for some of the sessions. Note to self: If you don’t have a reserved seat — come early (like really early). In the following I will give a short write up of the breakout sessions that I attended.</description></item><item><title>AWS re:invent 2017 — Day 0</title><link>/posts/2017-11-27_aws-re-invent-2017-day-0-e91baef32d54/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 06:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-11-27_aws-re-invent-2017-day-0-e91baef32d54/</guid><description>Welcome to Las Vegas
Our first full day in Las Vegas is over. It’s been a great day with time to explore the city and be a tourist before kicking off the AWS re:invent conference tomorrow.
Re:invent is going to be big. 40k-45k attendees. I’m guessing over 3/4 of the passengers of yesterdays flight from Stockholm to Las Vegas were attendees flying in.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading a HA Kubernetes Kops Cluster</title><link>/posts/2017-11-14_upgrading-a-ha-kubernetes-kops-cluster-9fb34c441333/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 17:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-11-14_upgrading-a-ha-kubernetes-kops-cluster-9fb34c441333/</guid><description>The Kubernetes release cadence is fast-paced with minor releases every quarter. Awesome! But how do I keep up?
Don’t worry, Kops makes it fairly easy to update your HA production cluster without any downtime (assuming you have scaled your deployments to a minimum of 2 pods per deployment).
This blog post will walk you through upgrading your Kubernetes cluster version 1.</description></item><item><title>CloudNativeCon + KubeCon Europe 2017</title><link>/posts/2017-04-02_cloudnativecon-kubecon-europe-2017-12c37c3af38c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 09:47:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-04-02_cloudnativecon-kubecon-europe-2017-12c37c3af38c/</guid><description>CloudNativeCon + KubeCon Europe 2017 is over! Wow, what a great conference. It was great to meet so many engaged and passionate people working the Cloud Native ecosystem.
In this post, we will try to give our perspective on the conference, by highlighting the key takeaways from the talks we attended.</description></item><item><title>HA Kubernetes Cluster on AWS? — Kops makes it easy</title><link>/posts/2017-03-12_ha-kubernetes-cluster-on-aws-kops-makes-it-easy-2337806d0311/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2017 17:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-03-12_ha-kubernetes-cluster-on-aws-kops-makes-it-easy-2337806d0311/</guid><description>In the first post of our mini-series about Kops, I demonstrated how you could set up a highly available Kubernetes cluster on AWS in an existing VPC leveraging the awesome open-source project Kops.
In order to demonstrate how this could be accomplished, I demonstrated how to set up all the networking, with VPC, subnets, route tables, etc.</description></item><item><title>Setting up a Highly Available Kubernetes Cluster with private networking on AWS using Kops</title><link>/posts/2017-01-30_setting-up-a-highly-available-kubernetes-cluster-with-private-networking-on-aws-using-kops-65f7a94782ef/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 19:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2017-01-30_setting-up-a-highly-available-kubernetes-cluster-with-private-networking-on-aws-using-kops-65f7a94782ef/</guid><description>This is the first post in a series of Kubernetes and Kubernetes Operations (Kops) related blog posts.
The purpose of this series is to provide a guide to setting up a production ready Kubernetes environment on AWS. There exists lots of options to accomplish this; among others, Techtonic, Kismatic, StackPoint Cloud, OpenShift, etc.</description></item><item><title>Installing a Kubernetes 1.4 cluster on Hypriot 1.1.1 with kubeadm</title><link>/posts/2016-12-15_installing-a-kubernetes-1-4-cluster-on-hypriot-1-1-1-with-kubeadm-b7495638610e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2016-12-15_installing-a-kubernetes-1-4-cluster-on-hypriot-1-1-1-with-kubeadm-b7495638610e/</guid><description>It’s been a while since our last blog post. However, we are back and again working with Kubernetes on a daily basis. This blog post will show you how to set up a Kubernetes 1.4 cluster with HypriotOS 1.1.1 and the new kubeadm tool.
Prerequisites A couple of Raspberry Pis (minimum two) A switch to connect the Raspberry Pis Cables for power and network For this tutorial we used 4 Raspberry Pi 3 and a Macbook Pro.</description></item><item><title>ContainerDays Hamburg</title><link>/posts/2016-07-13_containerdays-hamburg-c4639abae4fa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 18:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2016-07-13_containerdays-hamburg-c4639abae4fa/</guid><description>The first European ContainerDays was held in Hamburg (Germany) on June 27 and 28, 2016. The first day consisted of workshops about Kubernetes, Docker (security), DC/OS, rkt, and monitoring. The second day consisted of presentation sessions held by 16 different speakers. We went on a trip from Aarhus to Hamburg to check out the second day’s sessions.</description></item><item><title>Sneak preview</title><link>/posts/2016-06-12_sneak-preview-934354cac84c/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2016 10:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2016-06-12_sneak-preview-934354cac84c/</guid><description>It’s been a while since our last blog post. We have been crazy busy teaching a course about Microservices, Docker, Kubernetes, etc., using a Kubernetes Raspberry Pi cluster, named KubeCloud.
During this course we have evaluated the use of KubeCloud and how it can help students understand these different concepts. We have a lot of material that we will be sharing after the defense of our thesis at June 20th.</description></item><item><title>[Guide] Setting up a Kubernetes on ARM cluster on Raspberry Pis</title><link>/posts/2016-04-13_-guide-setting-up-a-kubernetes-on-arm-cluster-on-raspberry-pis-baac1511be3d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 13:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2016-04-13_-guide-setting-up-a-kubernetes-on-arm-cluster-on-raspberry-pis-baac1511be3d/</guid><description>This blog post will walk you through the steps of setting up kubernetes-on-arm that Luxas has created. Thanks to Luxas’ project it is pretty straightforward to get Kubernetes up and running on a Raspberry Pi. This guide will walk you through a fork of Luxas’ project, that contains minor adjustments to the DNS and a couple of extra scripts.</description></item><item><title>How to build a Raspberry Pi Cluster</title><link>/posts/2016-02-11_how-to-build-a-raspberry-pi-cluster-8af5f2f199d/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 08:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2016-02-11_how-to-build-a-raspberry-pi-cluster-8af5f2f199d/</guid><description>This guide will provide you with the stuff you need for putting a Raspberry Pi cluster together. The first thing you need is of course some Raspberry Pis . We choose to buy the Raspberry Pi 2 Model B, which is a pretty powerful little machine compared to the older Raspberry Pi.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the blog - and shopping tech!</title><link>/posts/2016-01-25_welcome-to-the-blog-and-shopping-tech/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 11:13:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2016-01-25_welcome-to-the-blog-and-shopping-tech/</guid><description>Welcome to our blog about the work we are about to begin within the subject of resilient cloud computing.
The title of our project is as follows: Resilient cloud computing in a controlled test environment
And what does that involve? That is a really good question, and a question we will start a quest for the next five month to answer this.</description></item></channel></rss>